http://www.alitex.co.uk/privacy-policy

Scandinavia
GreenhousesNational Trust CollectionNational Trust Greenhouse GalleryThe Hidcote (2.6m x 3m)The Scotney (2.6m x 4m)The Stourhead (2.6m x 5m)The Mottisfont (2.6m x 4m)The Tatton (2.9m x 5.1m)The Wimpole (2.9m x 6.4m)The Cliveden (3.5m x 6.4m)The Ickworth (2.9m x 7.1m)Browse AllBespoke GreenhousesGreenhouse PricingTraditional GreenhouseMessenger GreenhouseFreestanding GreenhousesLean to GreenhousesHexagonal and OctagonalGreenhouse ReplacementWalled GardensCommercial ProjectsBespoke Greenhouse DesignYour Greenhouse ProjectGreenhouse Paint Colour ChoicesGreenhouse Building WorksGreenhouse Case StudiesGreenhouse GalleryFAQsAccessoriesConservatoriesAftercareGreenhouse cleaning serviceUpdate your AlitexAlitex guaranteeGreenhouse & Accessory TutorialsArchitectsWorking with AlitexOur processDrawing office servicesAccreditations and credentialsManufacture and fabricationOur clientsCase studiesCombined greenhouse and conservatoryCruciform feature conservatoryGable ended Victorian style conservatoryHexagonal feature glasshouseHip ended traditional conservatoryPrice GuidelinesRegister for technical libraryArchitects loginNewsEventsBlogGreenhouse growing guideAlitex and the Chelsea Flower ShowVideosAbout UsThe Alitex experienceWorking with the National TrustRoyal Botanic Gardens, KewOur PeopleThe Alitex Paint CollectionContactBrochure requestBook a visitOur show site and factoryShow sites in the UK and IrelandAlitex around the world
Search form
Search
Greenhouses
National Trust Collection
National Trust Greenhouse Gallery
The Hidcote (2.6m x 3m)
The Scotney (2.6m x 4m)
The Stourhead (2.6m x 5m)
The Mottisfont (2.6m x 4m)
The Tatton (2.9m x 5.1m)
The Wimpole (2.9m x 6.4m)
The Cliveden (3.5m x 6.4m)
The Ickworth (2.9m x 7.1m)
Browse All
Bespoke Greenhouses
Greenhouse Pricing
Traditional Greenhouse
Messenger Greenhouse
Freestanding Greenhouses
Lean to Greenhouses
Hexagonal and Octagonal
Privacy policy
Here at Alitex, we take your privacy and data protection very seriously. This policy explains how and why we collect your information.
How Alitex collects information
We only collect information about you, from you. There a number of avenues in which you might show an interest in our products and request a brochure or communication from us at which point, we take a few details from you in order to fulfil this purpose. There are a few ways you might get in touch with us to request our goods, services or information: garden and flower shows, through our website contact forms, email, social media, on the phone or directly at our office at Torberry Farm.
What information we require
More often than not, you might get in touch with us in the first instance to request a brochure from us, which tells you about what we do and what products we offer. We email or post these out and it is up to you in that case what information you want to provide to us.
In order to send out our brochures, the minimum information we ask for is:
Your name
Your address (if you are requesting a brochure in the post)
Country of residence (so we know which colleague to hand your enquiry to)
Your email
Your telephone number. This is so a colleague can give you a call to ensure the brochure has arrived safely, find out a little more about your garden project and answer any questions you may have at this stage.
The details explained
We only ever use your personal information to administer your account and to provide the products, services or information you have requested from us.
We do not purchase data. Any information we have, is information you have shared with us.
We do not share your information with any third parties. We never have and we never will.
Your personal details are processed in the strictest of confidence by Alitex staff who are advised by our appointed internal Data Protection Manager.
Our products are defined by single glazed for a greenhouse or double glazed for a garden room conservatory. If you enquire through Alitex for a double glazed structure, your enquiry will be managed by our sister company Marston & Langinger, which together with Alitex, is owned under Alitex Manufacturing and managed and manufactured at our main Alitex office at Torberry Farm.
Transferring information outside the country
We supply our greenhouses around the world and have a number of dedicated partners employed by Alitex who work on our behalf in select countries. If you are in one of these countries which are managed by our partners, we will securely send your enquiry to this partners, otherwise your enquiry will be managed from our office.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites run by other organisations. The Alitex privacy policy applies only to our website‚ so we encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites you visit. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites.
How do I find out more?
You have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us.
We will only contact you for marketing purposes if you have given your consent.
If at any point you find you are receiving communications in error, would no longer like to hear from us, would like to update your details, would like to know what information we hold about you or even to be removed from our database, please contact us. We will put it right for you.
You can contact us by:
Email: enquiries@alitex.co.uk
Phone: 01730 826900
Post: Alitex Ltd, Torberry Farm, Petersfield, South Harting, Hampshire, GU31 5RG
We will always be transparent with you of any changes but if you would ever like to know more, please get in touch.
Request a brochure
Contact us to receive a greenhouse or conservatory brochure.
Request now >
Shows and Events
Friday, 18 December 2020 - 4:00pm to 5:00pm
SOLD OUT: Christmas cocktails with Mark Diacono
Find out more >
For more information
If you would like more information on our greenhouses or conservatories or have an enquiry please contact:
T: 01730 826900E: enquiries@alitex.co.uk
View blog >
What our clients say
I absolutely love the greenhouse. It is simply beautiful and I honestly feel that the garden was waiting for it all along. It sits perfectly into its space and is the jewel in the crown! I feel so excited by it and can't wait to fill it with exotic plants and complete the landscaping around it. Some of my friends have seen it and have been blown away by its loveliness!
Many thanks to Chris for all his hard work and dedication, and to the two great guys who installed it in super quick time. They are an asset to any team.
Mrs Power
Privacy policy
Accessibility
Cookie policy
Sitemap
© 2020 Alitex Limited. All rights reserved. The National Trust and oak leaf logos are trade marks of the National Trust (Enterprises) Limited and are used under licence by Alitex Limited.
